<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2018 Google Inc.
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~     http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->
<resources>
    <!-- App title -->
    <string name="app_name">exer2_palmes_b9l</string>

    <!-- Header -->
    <string name="header_name">Which Phineas and Ferb Character Are You ?</string>
    <string name="header2">You Are</string>

    <!-- Button label -->
    <string name="roll_label">Start</string>
    <string name="retry_label">Retry</string>

    <string name="blank">Find out which Character are you ! \n</string>
    <string name="name">Vince</string>

    <!-- Bio -->
    <string name="bio_phineas">Phineas Flynn-Fletcher is a young boy in the Flynn-Fletcher family. He is the son of Linda Flynn and step-son of Lawrence Fletcher.He is one of the three children of the Flynn-Fletcher household, along with his sister Candace
and step-brother Ferb. He shares a strong bond with the family pet, Perry the Platypus,
but remains unaware of his double life as a secret agent. \n\n
As an incurable optimist, Phineas constantly looks on the brighter side of things. He is also extremely smart, creative, persistent, and able to endeavor
 in immensely large projects and activities with the help of his step-brother. \n
His hospitality is a driving force behind many of his plans.
\n\n</string>

    <string name = "bio_ferb">
         Ferb Fletcher is a British child of the Fletcher family currently living
        in the American city of Danville. He is the step-son of Linda Flynn and
        son of Lawrence Fletcher. Being a native of England, he speaks with an
        English accent. He is one of three children of the Flynn-Fletcher household
        among his step-siblings and Candace Flynn. \n\n
        Ferb speaks very rarely, but is not actually shallow as others would assume.
        He is very courageous and has the ability to think quickly and stay calm in
        the midst of desperate scenarios. A notable skill of his is a technical and
        technological proficiency he shares with his stepbrother which he can easily
        take advantage of and build almost anything he chooses to. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name ="bio_candace">
        Candace Gertrude Flynn is the 15-year-old sister of Phineas Flynn and
        the step-sister of Ferb Fletcher. The eldest child of the Flynn-Fletcher
        household, \n
        she spends large portions of her time striving, but never succeeding to get her
        brothers in trouble for the things they do every day.
        \n\n
        A more successful venture that sometimes clashes with or overrides her
        need to bust her brothers, is her infatuation with Jeremy Johnson.
        While she isn\'\t doing these, she would often be seen conversing on the phone,
        or hanging out with Stacy Hirano and less often Jenny Brown, where she
        usually talks about Jeremy or tries to recruit their help in busting her
        brothers. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name = "bio_platypus">
        Perry the Platypus, code named Agent P, is Phineas and Ferb\'\s pet platypus,
        who, unbeknownst to his owners, lives a double life as a secret agent for
        the O.W.C.A. \n (The Organization Without a Cool Acronym a.k.a. "The Agency"),
        a government organization of animal spies. In the Agency, his immediate
        superior is Major Monogram. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name = "bio_doof">
        Dr. Heinz Doofenhmirtz is a 47 year old evil scientist hailing from the
        country of Drusselstein. He is the head of Doofenshmirtz Evil Incorporated.\n
        He tends not to be evil in the traditional sense, but rather overly dramatic,
        eccentric and generally clueless. His usual lair is an office building that he
        apparently owns, though he has worked from other locations when necessary for his
        plans. He attempts to wreak generally "evil" havoc and assert his rule across the
        entire Tri-State Area. Despite true dedication to this mission, almost all of his
        plans have been thwarted by his nemesis Perry the Platypus, though a few turn out
        to be successful in nature. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="bio_monogram">
        Major Francis Monogram or, as he likes to be known, simply Major Monogram
        (due to the fact that people often tease him about his first name) is Agent P\'\s
        commanding officer, and gives him his mission in each day. Helping him transmit
        his daily messages and do general things around the Agency is his intern, Carl.
    </string>

    <string name="bio_isabela">
         Isabella Garcia-Shapiro is the across-the-street neighbor and good friend
        of Phineas and Ferb. Isabella has a crush on Phineas; however, she doesn\'\t
        tell him. \n She\'\s the leader of Fireside Girls Troop 46231 and often
        volunteers to help in Big Ideas, usually with her troop being involved. \n\n
        Isabella is cheerful, fearless, quick-thinking, sweet, optimistic, and easy to
        get along with. She is always eager to help with Phineas and Ferb\'\s Big Ideas.
        When she participates with Phineas and Ferb in their endeavors, it\'\s either
        for the fun of it, accomplishment patches, or simply a way to be with Phineas.\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="bio_carl">
        Carl Karl, nicknamed Carl the Intern, Dr. Coconut and Squirrel-Man by
        Dr. Doofenshmirtz, is the hapless intern and cameraman of Major Monogram.
        He is an intern and is very loyal to Major Monogram.
        He works at the O.W.C.A. for college credit. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="bio_vanessa">
        Vanessa is sharp and sarcastic. Her behavior is comparable to that of a typical
        teenager. She cares about her reputation, having been upset when her clothes
        were mistakenly switched with Candace\'\s. Vanessa has always been found with the
        punk or goth crowd, as seen in her childhood photos and her friends\'\
        appearances \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="bio_baljeet">
        Baljeet is an Indian boy who always gets good grades and is constantly
        bullied by Buford. He\'\s considered a nerd and, for him, to get an F on a
        math test is the scariest thing known to man ("One Good Scare Ought to Do It!").
        He has moved here from India for his education. He can play various instruments,
        including the drums and the guitar. Although it seems like all his feelings make
        him want to do math, he actually just does a lot of math, "the feelings come
        and go"
    </string>
</resources>
